<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

  <channel>
    <title>zookfish's tank</title>
    <link>https://zookfish.com</link>
    <description>zooks website</description>
    <item>
      <title> Stop watching youtube</title>
      <link>https://zookfish.com/blog/2026-02-21post.html</link>
      <guid>https://zookfish.com/blog/2026-02-21post.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>
        <h1> I stopped watching youtube for 30 days</h1>
        <p>
          Funny enough the reason I stopped watching youtube was because of a youtube video. Props to Lrnjulie who made a
          video on what happened after 1 month without youtube.
        </p>
        <h2>Why?</h2>
        <p>
          I noticed that almost any moment I would get I would fill that time with a youtube video. Say while I’m cooking,
          eating, or even just walking outside. I would play and search for a youtube video.
        </p>
        <p>
          I wanted to change that and change how I wanted to relax but also make it easier for me to do the things that I
          want. Say maybe reading,coding, or walking in peace. But to just be in the moment.
        </p>
        <p>
          I was in a constant state of consumption and also lots of dopamine would be produced as well. I would scroll
          youtube for the “perfect” video to watch that would either entertain me or “change” my life.
        </p>
        <p>
          But that is not the case.
        </p>
        <h2> What I noticed after 30 days of no youtube</h2>
        <p>
          Like I said in my why statement, I learned that I had this sort of ritual. Whenever I got home I would open
          youtube and would find every opportunity to have a youtube video playing in the background. I always needed
          something to watch because it would just be a habit for me.
        </p>
        <p>
          I noticed during these 30 days that I will try to find other things to occupy my time. This was to delay working
          on
          activities that don’t produce instant gratification like maybe homework or even coding.
        </p>
        <p>
          After these 30 days, I really don’t feel the urge to scroll on youtube anymore. I rather do things that actually
          interest me.
        </p>
        <h2> Should you stop watching youtube</h2>
        <p>
          Yes I think you should stop watching youtube. Obviously I do condone youtube if you are actually using it
          intentionally to learn something. But to just open youtube with no sense of direction is where I draw the line.
        </p>
        <p>
          I’m going to stop counting the days now and just live a life where I’m not addicted to youtube. I think you should
          too.
        </p>
        <h2>What about other platforms</h2>
        <p>
          It’s obvious that you should not be on tiktok,instagram reels, and youtube shorts. Your attention is valuable and
          these are built to keep you from doing the things you want to do.
        </p>
        <p>Remember that you are
          loved and thanks for reading.
        </p>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I would go about losing weight in 2026</title>
      <link>https://zookfish.com/blog/2026-02-14post.html</link>
      <guid>https://zookfish.com/blog/2026-02-14post.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 01:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>
        If I had to condense everything I'd say figure out your tdee, eat at a deficit, weigh
        yourself daily,
        cook for your self, make sure your environment works for you(no snacks etc),track calories
        and weigh your food ,drink water, and get enough sleep. Remember that you are loved and
        thanks for reading.
      </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
